http://zardozz.com/zz/affiliates/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
— Staff at ZZ News and Reviews
Recent Articles:
WordPress Tutorial Videos
Quickbooks Online Recurring Payment Software
Best WordPress Website Hosting
Watching the News Can Be Hazardous to Your Health
DNC Shot Itself In The Foot!
Categories:
Cartoons (101)
Culture (68)
Downloads (12)
Editorial (77)
Internet (26)
iTunes (4)
News (1,094)
Politics (178)
Review (9)
Satire (207)
Sci/Tech (11)
Small Business Marketing (9)
Software (13)
Software Removal (3)
Archives & Search: Archives & Search:
Select Month
April 2017  (1)
March 2017  (1)
February 2017  (1)
January 2017  (2)
December 2016  (1)
October 2016  (1)
July 2016  (1)
June 2016  (2)
May 2016  (2)
March 2016  (2)
March 2014  (1)
October 2013  (1)
September 2013  (1)
August 2013  (2)
December 2012  (1)
September 2012  (1)
August 2012  (1)
July 2012  (1)
June 2012  (2)
May 2012  (2)
February 2012  (1)
December 2011  (2)
September 2011  (4)
June 2011  (3)
May 2011  (3)
April 2011  (1)
March 2011  (2)
February 2011  (2)
January 2011  (2)
December 2010  (1)
November 2010  (2)
October 2010  (5)
September 2010  (4)
August 2010  (7)
July 2010  (2)
June 2010  (2)
May 2010  (2)
April 2010  (4)
March 2010  (3)
February 2010  (2)
December 2009  (4)
October 2009  (2)
September 2009  (1)
August 2009  (1)
July 2009  (10)
June 2009  (6)
May 2009  (5)
April 2009  (2)
March 2009  (3)
February 2009  (4)
January 2009  (13)
December 2008  (6)
November 2008  (7)
October 2008  (6)
September 2008  (14)
August 2008  (14)
July 2008  (10)
June 2008  (7)
May 2008  (10)
April 2008  (16)
March 2008  (21)
February 2008  (7)
January 2008  (17)
December 2007  (22)
November 2007  (28)
October 2007  (39)
September 2007  (38)
August 2007  (24)
July 2007  (31)
June 2007  (31)
May 2007  (31)
April 2007  (50)
March 2007  (44)
February 2007  (25)
January 2007  (19)
December 2006  (41)
November 2006  (48)
October 2006  (27)
September 2006  (83)
August 2006  (50)
July 2006  (70)
June 2006  (44)
May 2006  (31)
April 2006  (34)
March 2006  (37)
February 2006  (25)
January 2006  (19)
December 2005  (35)
November 2005  (18)
October 2005  (23)
September 2005  (18)
August 2005  (14)
July 2005  (12)
June 2005  (12)
May 2005  (27)
April 2005  (23)
March 2005  (10)
February 2005  (19)
January 2005  (18)
December 2004  (15)
November 2004  (31)
October 2004  (17)
September 2004  (21)
August 2004  (16)
July 2004  (27)
June 2004  (22)
May 2004  (21)
April 2004  (3)
March 2004  (9)
February 2004  (18)
January 2004  (27)
December 2003  (2)
Search for:
